jorgecruise.com 2009-11-23

# Jorge Cruise: #1 bestselling author featured on oprah, today and cnn - Privacy

## Privacy Policy

JorgeCruise.com, Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Earning and maintaining your trust is important to us. We want you to understand what information we gather from you, how this information is used and protected. This Privacy Policy and Agreement ("Privacy Policy") discloses the privacy practices of the JorgeCruise.com. By using the Website, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by JorgeCruise.com online.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and therefore encourage you to revisit this page periodically or when you notice new features on the Website.

Please know that any information (including personal and health-related information) you reveal in a Website public forum (such as a message board, online meetings, posting, chat room/event, or similar electronic public venues) is not protected by this Privacy Policy. Such postings will be seen by Website members and/or guests and third parties not related to JorgeCruise.com. What you write could be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict, including to contact you for unauthorized purposes. Also, if you access a third party website from a link on the Website, any information you reveal on that site is not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should consult the privacy policy of each website you visit.

JorgeCruise.com, Inc. logs IP addresses (in other words, the location of your computer on the Internet) for system administration, troubleshooting, and to examine overall traffic trends. (For example, IP addresses help us determine the percentage of people coming from various online gateways, such as America Online or Yahoo!.) This information (in aggregate form) is recorded for administrative purposes only; IP addresses are not linked to any personal information.

You can browse the website and read our editorial content without registering or providing any personal information. However, in order to take advantage of our personalized services, you are required to provide us with personal information such as your email address. (We always let you know before we collect any personal information from you.) We collect similar information from users who choose to participate in our contests and promotional events.

What do we do with the information that we collect?  
The information we collect from your membership or surveys helps us to improve our content, customize content of certain pages for you, and to send you updates about the site.

Finally, the web site contains links to some other web sites. We cannot be responsible for the content of those sites or for the privacy of information that you may choose to share with them.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of our posted Privacy Policy, please contact us in any of the following ways:

Send an email to:  
support@jorgecruise.zendesk.com

Or, send a letter to:  
JorgeCruise.com, Inc.  
2924 Emerson Street, Suite 200  
San Diego, CA 92106   
Attn: Privacy / Legal

Or, send a fax to:  
(619) 374-2004   
Attn: Privacy / Legal

BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR WEBSITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES.

Effective Date: This policy was last updated on September 3, 2009
